IObit Driver Booster 10 Update History

V10.2 2023-01-10
+ Expanded database with more drivers for more new devices, like GeForce RTX 4070 Ti
+ Added more game-ready drivers for a better game experience, like The Witcher 3: Wild Hunt, Jurassic World Evolution 2, High on Life, Conqueror’s Blade, PUBG: Battlegrounds
+ Optimized the installation logic to improve the installation experience
+ Optimized the scan logic for a better scan experience
+ Fixed minor bugs

V10.1 2022-11-22
+ Supported new hardware drivers, including AMD Radeon™ RX 6000 Series and Nvidia GeForce RTX 40 Series
+ Added more game-ready drivers for a better game experience, like Call of Duty: Modern Warfare II, Overwatch® 2, Sackboy: A Big Adventure, Victoria 3, and FIFA 23
+ Optimized the scan logic for a faster scan
+ Minor UI improvements for a better user experience  
+ Fixed known bugs

V10.0 2022-09-27
+ Expanded database to support updating up to 8,500,000+ drivers for more devices
+ Added more drivers for Windows 11 and supported more new hardwares
+ Enhanced driver update to provide better game drivers and more stable drivers
+ Optimized scan to be up to 20% faster
+ Optimized update engine for 10% faster update and a much higher success rate
+ Accelerated the effect of Game Boost by up to 12%
+ Brand-new UI for a more user-friendly experience
+ Supported 38 languages
+ More can be discovered by you